https://atradersedge.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy NoticeIMPORTANT NOTICE CONCERNING PRIVACY OF INFORMATIONTrader’s Edge Incorporated (TE) strongly recognizes and respects the security and confidentiality of personal information that we collect and maintain concerning our clients and prospective clients. Maintainig your confidence and trust is a very high priority for us.INFORMATION SECURITYOnly those persons who must have the information to perform their job responsibilities are authorized to have access to data maintained within TE’s information files. TE maintains physical, electronic and procedural security measures that comply with federal regulations to safegaurd that information.INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECTAs a part of the serivces that TE provides, we obtain non-public personal information, which may include the following:Information you provide over the phone, via the Internet or on applications or other forms when you subscribe to TE’s sevices including name, address and wireless phone number.Check or wire information that you may provide in the process of conducting business with TE.Information needed to provide you with approval or account information that you provide over the phone, via the Internet or other forms during our relationship.INFORMATION THAT WE DISCLOSEIt is TE’s policy NEVER to sell, rent, lease, share or disclose the personal information of any client or prospective clients to any company not owned by, affliliated with or under a contractual relationship with TE. All the information that we collect and maintain on clients and prospective clients at TE may be used for the day-to-day operations of TE’s business as we provide our company’s services to you. In connection with this, we may also disclose personal information to affiliated an nonaffiliated third parties as required by law.MenuTraders EdgeAbout UsOur TeamAccount InformationDisclaimerPrivacy PolicyContact Us BackWhy Trader’s EdgeOptions EducationGlossaryAdditional Resources BackTrading ResourcesFAQNews & LinksWhy Commodities Over Stocks BackOpen & Closed Posted TradesFree OffersQuotes & ChartsCreate an Account
× Close Panel
